Guide to the Video Free Earth Production Company records, 1971-1991 MS2041
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Kenneth Rothschild papers, 1981-1991; MS2041 Series 2; 7 Linear feet
  - Printed Materials: Miscellaneous Files: Star Search Goddess, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials: Projects: Gaver, Chasen - Resumés, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials: Projects: Poetry Flash: The Bay Area's Poetry Review & Calender, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials: Projects: Publications/Reviewers of Tapes, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials: Artists/Clients: Bailey, Doug, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials: Artists/Clients: Barnick, Michael, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials: Artists/Clients: Barrows, David, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Bove, Robert and Noriro, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Brittain, Mark, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Canazal, John, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Chaves, Leonor, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Clark, Todd, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Craveri, Emily, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Cross, Carol, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Dale, Bruce, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Gage, Robert, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Garruba, Nancy, undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Gaver, Charles (Chasen), undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Gaver, Charles (Chasen), undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Gaver, Charles (Chasen), undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Gaver, Charles (Chasen), undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Gaver, Charles (Chasen), undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Guidone, Jack, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Hagedorn, Jeff, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Higgs, Bill, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Hudson, Andrew, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Kernan, Margot, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Lambda Rising, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Lanz, Joseph, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Lanz, Joseph, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Lanz, Joseph, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Lanz, Joseph, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Malone, Isabel-Lee, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Malone, Isabel-Lee, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Malone, Isabel-Lee, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Mayer, Jim - L.A., undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Palmer, Kathleen, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Ramsey, Margaret, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Schneiderman, Sarah, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Schneiderman, Sarah, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Sherry, Patrick, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Sobin, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Stenstrom, Ruth, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Stirling, Prosser, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Vanderbilt, David, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Walters, Kathy, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Williams, James, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Wolkoff, Hunter, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials:Artists/Clients: Woodward, Stanley, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: AIVF, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Association of MDArea Media Artists, Inc. (AMAMA), undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Art Com Television, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Art Com Television, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Arts Group (B&M), undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Arna Vodenos Productions Inc. (AVP), undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Axolotl, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Chrysalis Arts Group, undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Cultural Alliance, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Downtown Community TV NYC, undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: DC Art Center, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: DC Cable, undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: DC Contemporary Dance Theatre, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Everyday Theatre, undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Fondo Del Sol, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Fondo Del Sol, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Fondo Del Sol, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Hazard, Mike-Minnesota, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Independent Media Producers Association, Inc (IMPA), undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: In Motion, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: ITVA, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Joy of Motion, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Maryland (MD) Writer's Council, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Osiris, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Source Theatre, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Sanctuary Theatre, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Theatre Development Fund, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Video Data Bank, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Video Magazine/Washington Project for the Arts (WPA), undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Video Magazine/Washington Project for the Arts (WPA), undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Printed Materials:Organizations: Video Windows-Active, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Printed Materials:Completed Productions: Thru the CRT, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Printed Materials:Completed Productions: Under Suspicion, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Printed Materials:Completed Productions: Vicki Picks a Tie, 1984 November (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Printed Materials:Completed Productions: VIDEO-D (From Rockets & Dogs II), 1984 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials:Completed Scripts: Celebrity Nudes, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials:Completed Scripts: Constant Interruption, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials:Completed Scripts: Constant Interruption, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials:Completed Scripts: Constant Interruption; Background, Notes, Dialogue Ideas, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials:Completed Scripts: Hugs, 1982 April (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials:Completed Scripts: Hugs [Rev.], 1982 September (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials:Completed Scripts: Lunch with June East, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials:Completed Scripts: Manhattan Memories, 1982 August (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials:Completed Scripts: Round Trip to Nowhere, 1983 July (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials:Completed Scripts: Washington Wives, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Actor/Director Resumés, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Actor/Director Resumés, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Advertising, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Cable Notes, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Cable Notes, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Competitors, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Equipment Notes, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Legal Notes, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Music Recording Studios, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Music Rights, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Music Scores, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Press Clips (of VFE tapes) originals, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Public Relations (Press release), undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Rates/ Studios/ Services, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Real Estate Notes, Contracts, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Sales Rep., undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Sales Rep. Old Resumé, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Talent, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Talent Clippings, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Tape Inventory, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Tape Loan Log, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials:General Material: Tape Orders, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials:Distribution: Distribution Letters, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials:Distribution: Distribution Notes, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials:Distribution: Festivals, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Printed Materials:Distribution: Follow Up Sources, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Printed Materials:Distribution: Non Broadcast: Festivals Galleries, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Printed Materials:Distribution: Published Sources, undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Printed Materials:Distribution: Tape Distribution for Dist., undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Printed Materials:Distribution: Videotape Catalog/Aims, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Printed Materials:Fund Raising: Contributors VFE Arts, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Printed Materials:Fund Raising: Investors, undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Printed Materials:Arts Records: VFE Arts Records, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Printed Materials:Arts Records: VFE Arts Records, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials:Arts Records: VFE Arts Records, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials: Business Contacts, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials: Business Notes, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials: Business Notes, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials: Business Notes, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials: Business Notes, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials: Business Notes, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials: Correspondence, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials: Video Correspondence, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials: Video Correspondence, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials: Video Correspondence, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials:Correspondence: Washington Area Film/Video League (WAFVL), undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials:Correspondence: Washington Center, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials:Correspondence: Washington Project for the Arts (WPA), undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials:Correspondence: WETA, Ch. 26, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials:Correspondence: Whitman-Walker-Beat, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials:Correspondence: WHMM, Ch. 32, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials:Correspondence: Wooly Mammoth Theatre Company, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials:Correspondence: Writers Guild, West, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials:Correspondence: WTVS, Ch. 56, Detroit, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials:Correspondence: Zais, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials: Activity Log Forms, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials: Expenses Forms, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials: Petty Cash Forms, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials:Grants: Beat Grant Applications, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials:Grants: Beat Grant Enclosures, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials:Grants: Beat NEA Grant, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials:Grants: Chicago Resource Center, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials:Grants: D.C. Commission Grant, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials:Grants: D.C. Commission Grant, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Printed Materials:Grants: D.C. Commission Grant Application, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Printed Materials:Grants: D.C. Commission Grant, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Printed Materials:Grants: D.C. Commission Grant, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Printed Materials:Grants: D.C. Commission Grantees, undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Printed Materials:Grants: D.C. Community Humanities Council (DCCHC) - Final, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Printed Materials:Grants: D.C. Grant NEA Guideline, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials:Grants: Grants (misc.), undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials:Grants: Letters of Recommendation -Video Grants, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials:Grants: Strong Foundation, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials:Mailing Lists: California, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials:Mailing Lists: Christmas List Cards, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials:Mailing Lists: Literary Centers, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials:Mailing Lists: Mailing Info., undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials:Mailing Lists: New York List, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials:Mailing Lists: Old Mailing Lists, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials:Mailing Lists: Old Mailing Lists, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials:Mailing Lists: Press/Business List, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials:Business - General: American Film Institute (AFI) Workshop Notes, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Printed Materials:Business - General: Brush Report, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials:Business - General: Business, Tax Information, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials:Business - General: D.C. & Federal Small Business Information, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials:Business - General: Financial Statements, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials:Business - General: SIC Codes, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials:Business - General: University of the District of Columbia (UDC) Business Seminars, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 6)